http://www.emmagoldman.com/about/privacy.html

click for map to clinicinfo@emmagoldman.com
Hours:
Monday-Friday
9am - 5pm
Some Saturdays (call first)
Search our site:
home / about us / privacy
Privacy Policy
Emma Goldman Clinic has a firm commitment to privacy. We take your privacy concerns seriously and want to make every effort to address them. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting www.emmagoldman.com you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
Collecting and Using Personal Information
We appreciate your interest in the Emma Goldman Clinic. When you visit and
online store or our donations Web page.
Financial information shared through transactions in our online store and
donations page are protected through a secure server. Any non-public personal
information that you may provide via our sites will be used solely for the
purpose stated on the page where it is collected. We will not disclose
any personal information without your advance permission except when we believe
the law requires us to do so or the disclosure is necessary to protect the
rights or property of the Emma Goldman Clinic.
What User Information Do
We Have?
Our logging software recognizes the home
server of visitors, but not their e-mail addresses or their identities. We may
collect information such as the time of your visit, the amount of time you spend
on the emmagoldman.com Web site and any errors encountered. This information is
kept strictly confidential.
We may also collect a user’s e-mail
address or other personal information if the user makes a purchase at our online
store or makes a donation. When you use our website's shopping cart, we place a
small data file called a "cookie" on your computer to match your browser to your
shopping cart for that session. Once you close your browser, this cookie expires
and no longer has any effect.
E-mail
Privacy
The Emma Goldman Clinic does not rent, sell, barter or give away its users’
e-mail addresses for use by outside parties for any purpose.
We welcome your comments or questions about our websites and services and
have provided an e-mail for that purpose. We will share your comments and
questions with those employees
most capable of addressing your questions
and concerns.
permission while in transit to us. For that reason,
to protect your privacy,
please do not use e-mail to communicate information
to us that you consider
confidential. If you wish, you may contact us instead
via non-cellular
telephone at 1.800.848.7684 or 319.337.2111.
disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this policy. We
intend to
cooperate with all law enforcement inquiries and with other third
parties as
we believe necessary in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual
property rights infringement or any other activity that is illegal or
may
expose the Emma Goldman Clinic to legal liability.
Data or information supplied on our
Web site also may be subject to
eavesdropping, tampering, spamming, forgery,
hacking, harassment, fraud, and
other limitations of the security and/or
authentication features of our system.
the Emma Goldman Clinic,
Attn: Development at 227 North Dubuque Street,
time.
Links to Other Internet
Web Sites
Other Internet Web sites or services that
may be accessible through emmagoldman.com have separate data and privacy
policies.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or
concerns about this privacy policy, please feel
free to contact us
at:
Last updated: September 27,
2007
